Hello, hello.
どうも、こんにちは
Hello.
こんにちは
Good evening.
こんばんは
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
fine?
元気?
Yeah.
うん
How well are you doing?
どれくらい元気ですか?
fine.
元気
Are you full of energy?
元気いっぱい?
Yeah.
うん
You've lost weight, haven't you?
やっぱ痩せたよね?
I might have lost weight.
痩せたかも
I did lose weight.
やっぱ痩せたわ
I'm thin.
痩せてる
But my boobs are getting bigger.
でもおっぱい大きくなってる
Yay!
やったー
That's amazing.
すごいね
Cosplay is really good.
やっぱコスプレいいっすね
Today, I feel like I'm going to have a little fun with cosplay.
今日はね、ちょっとコスプレでぶちかましていこうかなという感じ
But.
なんです けど
It suits you.
似合ってるね
Yeah.
うん
Have you ever done that?
今までしたことある?
do not have.
ない
Isn't there?
ないの?
Yeah.
うん
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうなんだ
It looks good with everything.
なんかなんでも似合いそう
Something like that.
なんすとか
nice.
いいね
It seems normal, normal.
なんか普通に、普通にいそう
I feel like it's going to happen this time.
なんか今回にいそう
Usually more than this time.
普通に今回以上っすね
Wow, that's good.
いやーいいっすね
Take off your mask.
マスクとって
It really suits you.
やっぱ似合ってるね
Yeah.
うん
It really suits you.
めっちゃ似合ってるっすよ
So cute.
かわいいっすね
So can I have you stand one more time?
じゃあちょっともう一回立ってもらっていい?
It's really amazing.
やっぱすごい
Well then, let's get some tongue out.
じゃあちょっとベロ出してみて
nice.
いいね
So today, I had a little request.
じゃあちょっと今日は、 ちょっとリクエストがあったんですよ
I had a request.
リクエストがあった
Can I have this for a moment?
これちょっと持ってもらっていい?
This, this is Cusco.
これ、これがクスコです
Have you ever used it?
使ったことある?
There isn't.
ないよ
ないよね
It's about looking at pussies.
それ、おまんこを見るやつなんですよ
I'd like to take a look at your pussy,
ちょっとおまんこ見ていきたいんですけど、
Is that okay?
いいですかね
Yes.
はーい
It's plastic, isn't it?
プラスチックなんですよね
There's also a silver one, but today I'm going with a plastic one.
銀のやつもあるんだけど、 今日はちょっとプラスチックのやつで
I'll do it.
やって いきます
Yes.
はーい
Okay?
いいっすか
yes.
はい
What, are you losing your hair?
え、脱毛してる?
Um, I might have done it before.
あの、前したかも
You probably grew older, right?
お前さ、もっと生えてたよね、多分
Isn't your pussy really shaved?
なんかめっちゃパイパンになってない?
Eh.
えー
Haven't you done it recently?
最近はしてない?
最近してない?
Are you shaving?
剃ってる?
I haven't shaved.
剃ってない
Oh, aren't you shaving?
あ、剃ってない?
It's so beautiful.
すげーきれいじゃん
I guess it came off in a good way.
いい感じに抜けたのかな
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Yeah.
うん
I'll add a little bit.
ちょっと入れていきます
So, can you hold it here for a moment?
じゃあ ちょっとここ持っててもらっていい?
From below.
下からね
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
It's so beautiful inside the mancon.
マンコンの中めっちゃきれいじゃん
I have a very small neck.
す げーちくびが
Come here and lick me.
こっち来てさ、ちくびなめで
Take a little lick.
ちくびなめをちょっと取って
It's reflected.
映るよね
That's right, you can just hang around there.
そうそうそう、そこらんぐりでいい
Look at the camera.
カメラ見てね
Yes, let's look at the camera.
そう、カメラ見ようか
Cheer up here.
こっちに気上げてね
Yeah.
うん
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
This system may be tough.
この体制きついかもしれないけど
Wow.
うわー
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Then take a look for yourself.
じゃあちょっと自分でずっと見て
Yeah, look.
うん、 見て
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Yeah.
うん
Where can I take it out?
どこ出していい?
middle.
中
Can I cum inside you?
中出していい?
Yeah.
うん
Are you going to get violent?
激しくいっちゃうの?
Yeah.
うん
nice.
いいね
Yeah.
うん
go.
いく
Finally, please give us your thoughts.
じゃあ最後、感想お願いします
Thank you for your hard work.
お疲れさまでした
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
cold?
寒い?
Yeah.
うん
It's cold, isn't it?
寒いよね
So, can I have a nonce next time?
じゃあちょっと今度ナンスやっていいですか?
yes.
はい
Please show me your breasts one last time.
ちょっと最後おっぱい見せてね
Ah, nice.
あ、いいね
My boobs are getting bigger.
おっぱいやっぱ大きくなってるわ
Feels good.
いい感じ
Well, instead of doing cosplay for the last time, let's do cosplay again next time.
じゃあ最後コスプレじゃなくて、今度コスプレまたやろうね
Yes.
はーい
May I?
いいですか?
Yeah.
うん
Well then, goodbye for the last time.
じゃあ最後バイバイ
bye bye.
バイ バイ
good night.
おやすみなさい